Ah
About what was said tonight
Ming Yao heard it clearly
Mrs. Fu handled it well
I wasn't establishing authority for her
I was giving her a chance to let
others see her clearly
Still working right after the banquet
Someone expects me to make a fool of myself tomorrow
This project is a bit weird
The budget increased too fast
The supplier list changes frequently
Third-party tech
service fee percentage is also high
Notice anything
I can't say it right now
But this project is
perfect for testing you
And perfect to sound me out too
Let's find evidence first
What's so funny
Nothing
Just thinking someone will be disappointed tomorrow
Heh